ILGWU Related Sound Recordings 6036/073 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pins and Needles, 27 (Box 3)
  Sing Me A Song With Social Significance, Doing The Reactionary, One Big Union For Two, It's Better With A Union Man, Nobody Makes A Pass At Me, I've Got The Nerve To Be In Love, Not Cricket To Picket, Back To Work, Statues Quo; Mene, Mene, Tenkel
- "Truman Barkley and Labor" October 7, 14, 21, 28, 28 (Box 3)
  ILGWU Campaign Committee Secretary of Labor M.J. Tobin and Humphrey Bogert; Senator Hubert Humphrey and Ronald Reagan; President Harry Truman and Tallulah Bankhead; Alben Barkley and Melvyn Douglas and Helen Douglas
- Antonini Speech 7/18/1946, 1 (Box 4)
  Part 2
- Welcome Home to Luigi Antonini, 2 (Box 4)
  Copy 1; 2 sided
- A Welcome Home to Luigi Antonini, 3 (Box 4)
  Copy 2; 2 sided
- A Welcome Home to Luigi Antonini, 4 (Box 4)
  Cop 3; 2 sided
- Italian Hour, Alfredo Antonini 11/24/45, 5 (Box 4)
  10:30 AM; WEVD; Part 1
- Italian Hour, Alfredo Antonini 11/22/45, 6 (Box 4)
  10:30 AM; WEVD; Part 2
- Hometown 5/11/56, 7 (Box 4)
  26th ILGWU Convention by the Northeast Department, Atlantic City N.J.; Jim Corbett; Weldon Reilly; 2 sided
- Red Mikado, 8 (Box 4)
  Harold J. Rome; Pins & Needles; Robert H. Gordon; Simon Rady; 2 sided
- Red Mikado, 9 (Box 4)
- The Story of Hancock, Maryland, by the ILGWU, 10 (Box 4)
  J. J. Edelman
- The Story of Hancock, Maryland, by the ILGWU, 11 (Box 4)
- Twentieth Anniversary Local 32 ILGWU 2/20/1954, 12 (Box 4)
  Hotel Commodore; 6 sides; 3 records
- "Truman, Barkley and Labor" October 7. 14. 21. 28, 13 (Box 4)
  ILGWU 1948 Campaign Committee; President Harry S. Truman; Vice President Alben W. Barkley; Secretary of Labor Maurice J. Tobin; U.S. Senator Hubert H. Humphrey; Tallulah Bankhead; Humphrey Bogart; Helen Gahagan Douglas and Melvyn Douglas; Ronald Reagan; ""Have a Heart Taft Hartley written and sung by Jack Lawrence; Produced by M.S. Novik; 2 Records; 4 sides
- Inaugural of Seaman's House in London, 14 (Box 4)
  5 sides; 3 records